<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Content on Shiba Kushti</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Content on Shiba Kushti</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 12:06:47 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Read all of the below then click here!</title>
      <link>/educate-yourself/read-all/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/educate-yourself/read-all/</guid>
      <description>Do you now understand your risks and assumptions? Head on over to https://t.me/ErgoTokenCentre - send a message that you understand Crypto assets related risks along with your address, and receive some Shiba Kushti&amp;rsquo;s! (Only 1000 in circulation)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Common Scams</title>
      <link>/educate-yourself/common-scams/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/educate-yourself/common-scams/</guid>
      <description>A list of tactics used to try scam you out of your tokens Remember: if it&amp;rsquo;s too good to be true, it most likely is!
Youtube Another common tactic is fake giveaways, in which you send tokens first, and will receive 2x, 5x, 10x etc. back. This is made to look legitimate, with an Authority Figure (the following example is just a random video of Hoskinson), Social Proof (It looks like lots of people are currently watching and liked the stream, however this is all bots).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>General Security</title>
      <link>/educate-yourself/general-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/educate-yourself/general-security/</guid>
      <description>Keep your recovery phrase in a secure offline location When you create a wallet on Daedalus you will receive a recovery phrase, this is a list of 24-words that are used to generate the private key to access your funds. Anyone who has your recovery phrase can access your funds and create transactions, so you must keep it safe and secure. This is of crucial importance!
  Create your wallets ONLY on a trusted system</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy</title>
      <link>/educate-yourself/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/educate-yourself/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Blockchain: A Problem Or The Solution? When one uses a centralized exchange to buy or sell crypto for fiat, they’ll have to go through a KYC (Know Your Customer) process, which will reveal their identity. In some aspects, Bitcoin and other public blockchains are not suitable for money laundering and other malicious activities . Criminals will still need to go through regulated corporations to cash out any ill-gotten funds or spend them on any real-world items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pump and Dumps</title>
      <link>/educate-yourself/pumpdump/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/educate-yourself/pumpdump/</guid>
      <description>A pump and dump scheme involves buying a low-market cap asset and later inflating the asset’s price. Investors usually artificially inflate the price of a crypto asset and sell it to unsuspecting investors, right before the asset suddenly crashes. Often, the promise of high returns from these schemes attracts inexperienced traders. These traders are left counting their losses, once the crypto asset crashes, as planned by the pump and dump group.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Questions to ask</title>
      <link>/educate-yourself/questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Aug 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/educate-yourself/questions/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of some of the responses to the ErgDex Beta Launch Competition: Know your Risks and Assumptions! u/InThePortalAgain
  Generally if a project advertises flashy user interfaces and videos without substance such as thoughtful whitepapers and substantial evidence of real development, I get very suspicious. If a token has built in protocols to make it more difficult to sell to discourage selloffs I get suspicious. Any kind of artificial token burn to inflate market cap I get suspicious.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
